it's time to play panium
panium you know for most people their
37th birthday celebration is nothing
more than a reheated slice of pizza and
the silbering reminder that they are
half in the ground and completely
irrelevant to advertisers how would I
know I'm 29 but
[Laughter]
hey well that wasn't the I hosted single
out when I was
nine but that wasn't the case when ja ja
the panda turned 37 years old this week
and blew up the internet ja ja spent the
day eating more cake and bamboo than you
can shake it a stick of bamboo at uh she
was also awarded the Guinness world
record for oldest living panda in
captivity oh I think pandas are adorable
I'm not a monster or a dentist I just
think the oldest no seriously that guy
someone should put that guy's head on a
agree uh can we talk about for a second
look at how sad this cake
is this I
do think the Panda's like ah he said red
Velvet the is this what you I say I got
a bunch of
carrot I just think oldest living panda
in captivity is pretty unimpressive as
far as world records go comedians your
challenged to give me some less
impressive Guinness Records I'm put 60
seconds on the clock and begin Kurt uh
most Wilco played in a coffee
shop sto uh marus Mark points Kurt
tenderous loin points chis andest dick
points Jimmy uh most uncles named Rick
points Chris bestiest Best Buy uh oh no
points from the audience on that was
Jimmy uh least convincing that's what
she
said
Jimmy uh sidus boob
okay
boob